Guide to the Samuel Slie Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Addendum - 2010, Series VI
  - Battell Chapel / Church of Christ at Yale
    - Songbooks, Sponsorships, Bible Study (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - B
    - Bibliographies (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Black Church at Yale (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Black Church at Yale (Box 32, Folder 1-2)
    - Black Issues (see also "Africa," "South Africa," "Course-Related: Black Studies," "New Haven Civil Rights") (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Black Faculty (Box 32, Folder 4-5)
    - Black Seminarians (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Black Students, Black Coalition, Yale Civil Rights Council (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Black Church, Seminarians, Course Material (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Black Americans (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Black Theology (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - C
    - Civil Rights, Racism: Resources, Correspondence (Box 33, Folder 4-7)
    - Civil Rights, Racism: Resources, Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 1-5)
    - Civil Rights: Resources, Wilmington 10, Fundraising Letters (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Civil Rights, Racism (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Connecticut Mental Health Center Clergy Liaison Project (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Campus Ministry and Higher Education (Box 35, Folder 3-5)
    - Campus Ministry and Higher Education (Box 36, Folder 1-3)
    - Campus Ministry and Higher Education, Catholic (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Campus Ministry – Field Education (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Campus Ministry – Non-Yale (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Casa Materna orphanage, Naples (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Christian Community Action (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Christian Ministry in Higher Education (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Church Programs Served (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Clippings (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Coalition Against Apartheid (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Coffin, William Sloane, Jr. Yale University Chaplain (see also "General Correspondence," "Sermons," "Yale," and "Yale University") (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Cogna work seminar, Tuscany (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Consortium Community Counselees (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Course-Related (Box 38, Folder 1-3)
    - Course-Related: Ministry in Higher Education (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Course Related: American College Students (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Course Related: United Church of Christ Polity, 1980-1984 (Box 39, Folder 1-2, 5-6)
    - Course Related: South Africa Study Tour (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Course Related: South Africa Investment Seminar (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Course Related: Various (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Culinary Institute of America (Box 39, Folder 8-9)
  - D
    - Desk Calendar, 1969-1971 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Desk Calendar, 1971-1985 (Box 40, Folder 1-5)
    - Death (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Deering Conference Center, New Hampshire: Applicants (Box 40, Folder 7-8)
    - Deering retreat center, New Hampshire, 1962-1969, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 1-9)
    - Deering retreat center, New Hampshire, 1958-1967 (Box 42, Folder 1-5)
    - Disarmament and Conversion, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Dissent, 1964-1965 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Downtown Cooperative Ministry, 1984-1990 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Dwight Hall, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - E
    - Elderly (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - The Exit coffeehouse, 1965 - 1968 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - F
    - Faith and Finance (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Freshman Conference, 1969- (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Funerals (Box 44, Folder 3-4)
  - G
    - General Correspondence (Box 44, Folder 5-6)
    - General Correspondence (Box 45, Folder 1-4)
    - General Correspondence, including Bart Giamattei (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - H
    - Hillhouse High School (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Hospitals (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - I
    - Installations (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Intercollege (Box 45, Folder 7-8)
    - Italiano (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - L
    - Letterhead (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Liberation Theology (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - M
    - Methodist Student Loan Fund (Box 46, Folder 2-3)
    - Ministry to Blacks in Higher Education (MBHE) (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous inspirational clippings, posters, postcards, poems (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Missions (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Morse College (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Music (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - N
    - New Haven Alcohol Clinic (Box 46, Folder 9-10)
    - New Haven Alcohol Clinic (Box 47, Folder 1-4)
    - New Haven Civil Rights/Racism (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - New Haven: Black Panthers Trial / Riots (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - New Haven Clergy Association (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - New Haven Association UCC Churches/ Ministers (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - New Haven Council of Churches (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - New Haven Ecumenical Structure Committee (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - New Haven Human Services Policy Council (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Northern Student Movement (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - New England School Religious Education (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - O
    - Ordination (Box 66, Folder 4-8)
    - Ordination (Box 67, Folder 1-3)
  - P
    - Packard Manse (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Paier College (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Personal and Photos (Box 67, Folder 6-7)
    - Poland (Box 47, Folder 9-10)
    - Poland (Box 48, Folder 1-5)
    - Prayers (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Prayers/Invocations (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Q
    - Quinnipiac College (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - R
    - Recommendations (Box 49, Folder 2-7)
    - Recommendations (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Resume, Misc. letters (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - S
    - Secretary - Seminaries (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Sermons – Collected (Box 50, Folder 4-5)
    - Sermons by Slie (Box 50, Folder 6-8)
    - Sermons by Slie (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Sexuality (Box 51, Folder 2-4)
    - Socio-Economic Issues (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - South Africa Resources (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - South Africa: National Initiatives on South Africa, New Haven South Africa Task Force, Yale Task Force on South Africa (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - South Africa: Yale Investments (Box 52, Folder 3-6)
    - South Africa: Yale Investments (course material) (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - South Africa: Documents and Resolutions, UCC Materials, Company Reports, Bibliography (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - South Africa: Yale Investments (Box 53, Folder 3-5)
    - South Central Community College/Speakers (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Spiritual Direction (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Southern Connecticut State College (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Springfield College (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Students YCC/Summer Service (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - T
    - Taize (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Talks (Box 54, Folder 4-5)
    - Teilhard de Chardin (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - U
    - United Church of Christ Board for World Ministries (Box 54, Folder 7-8)
    - United Church of Christ Board for World Ministries (Box 55, Folder 1-3)
    - United Church of Christ Churches (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - United Church of Christ - Racial Justice/CT Conference, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - United Church of Christ - National (Box 55, Folder 6-7)
    - United Church of Christ - National (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - United Ministries in Higher Education (UMHE) (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - UMHE in Greater New Haven – including financial records (Box 56, Folder 3-6)
    - United Nations Association (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Unified Family (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Unification Church (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - United Church on the Green (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - University of New Haven (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Urban League (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - V
    - Vannorsdall, John (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Vietnam Draft (Box 57, Folder 8-9)
    - Vietnam - Conscientious Objectors (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Vocational Counselees (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - W
    - Weddings (Box 58, Folder 1-7)
    - Wedding Resources (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Wider City Parish (Box 59, Folder 2-3)
    - Worship Resources (Box 59, Folder 4-6)
    - Worship Resources (Box 60, Folder 1-4)
  - YMCA
    - Correspondence (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Programs, meetings (Box 60, Folder 6-7)
    - Programs, meetings (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - International (Box 61, Folder 2-7)
    - Northeast Region (Box 61, Folder 8-9)
    - Long Range Plans (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - National Council (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Task Force (Student/Young Adult) (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Reports, 1983-1984 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - International Committee (Box 62, Folder 5-8)
    - YMCA and Yale Religious Ministry (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - YMCA Miscellaneous (Box 63, Folder 2-5)
    - YMCA Miscellaneous (Box 64, Folder 1-4)
  - Yale
    - Miscellaneous (Box 64, Folder 5-6)
    - Committee on Cultural Relations with Poland (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Council on Community Affairs (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Divinity School (Box 65, Folder 2-3)
    - Faculty Club – Yale Club New Haven (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Religious ministry (Box 65, Folder 5-8)